googletopper.com 2014-05-08

# Privacy Policy — Google Detonator V2.0

**_Welcome to  [www.GoogleTopper.com](http://www.listdetonator.com/) _**

For the purpose of clarification wherever you see the words ‘you’, ‘your, ‘visitor’ or ‘user’ it refers to ‘you’.  Whereas where ever you see the terms ‘we’ or ‘our’ it refers to Bright Spark Marketing, LLC. 

We acknowledge that online privacy is a key concern for our users, and we are committed to ensuring the protection of your privacy at all times. This statement governs our privacy policies regarding all visitors to our site whether they are paying customers or otherwise. 

**  
Personally Identifiable Information  
**Bright Spark Marketing, LLC collects certain ‘Personally Identifiable Information’.  Personally Identifiable Information refers to any information that can be used to identify, contact or locate the person to whom such information pertains. 

This information includes but is not limited to their; names, address, phone number, email, fax, social security number, payment details and credit card information. 

Personally Identifiable Information excludes demographic information Specific information collected from paying customers includes: billing name, billing address, phone, email and the credit card information / payment details required to authorize purchases and transact payments for products and services. 

**Third Party Data Collection**  
Third party service providers such as banks and credit card companies may collect information from our site visitors and paying customers.  This information is necessary in order to facilitate the provision of credit, insurance or escrow services.

We do not control how these third party vendors use the date collected, but we do ask them provide full disclosure on how they use such information. Furthermore certain third parties are merely link in the distribution chain and do not store, retain or use any information collected through our site.

**  
How We Use Personally Identifiable Information  **  
Personally Identifiable Information is used to transact authorized payment, to facilitate the provision of our services and to enhance our service offering.  Site visitor and customers may be contacted on occasion with information pertaining to the subject matter.

This can take the form of research, customer service or any information pertaining to our service offering.

**  
With whom may the information be shared?**  
Information may only be shared with authorized third party vendors that are essential to the provision of services for which the authorized customer is transacting.

We may also share such information with one of our other companies, in order to offer you related products or services that may be of interest to you. We may share aggregated information pertaining to our visitors / customers demographics with affiliated agencies and third party vendors.

‘Opt Out’ opportunities are provided to enable you to halt communications form us or some other agency acting on our behalf.

**  
How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by [www.GoogleTopper.com](http://www.listdetonator.com/) is stored on our high security servers and is not accessible by third parties or employees of Bright Spark Marketing, LLC, for any purpose other than that aforementioned.

**  
Visitor Consent Re: Data Collections and Dissemination  
**Visitors and authorized customer may elect to contact our helpdesk at any time if they will to opt out from receiving unsolicited information or from being contacted by us, our vendors or any third party agencies.

**  
The Use of Cookies**  
GoogleTopper.com uses cookies to determine the preferences of our site visitors.  Cookies are also used for security purposes to protect authorized customers. Cookies are used for a variety of reasons.

We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. This includes automated logging out of users inactive for a certain period of time.

**  
The Use of Login Information  
**GoogleTopper.com uses login information including but not limited to ISPs, IP addresses and browser types in order to analyzes trends, record demographic information, determine user preferences, track a user’s site usage, administer the site as well as several other important uses.

**  
Disclosure to Law Enforcement Agencies**  
If required we will disclose personally identifiable information to law enforcement agencies in order to comply with a course order or subpoena.

**  
The Security of Personally Identifiable Information**  
Our employees are governed by strict security protocols.  Only a small number of qualified employees have access to the information via a secure password. Sensitive financial information such as credit card numbers is protected via the latest encryption protocols.

While every possible measure is taken to secure our site, electronic data by its nature is subject to errors / tampering thus we cannot guarantee that such event will not occur and we will not be liable to visitor or customers for any such occurrences.

**  
The Correction of Inaccurate Information**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers can request the correction of inaccurate information or the deletion of certain personally identifiable information by raising a ticket at our help desk.  It is possible however given the nature of backups and records of deletions that some residual data will be retained.

**  
Changes to** **  the Privacy Policy**  
Visitors and authorized customer will be informed of any changed made to this Privacy Policy, via our web site.
